Brother-in-law
This is a 20-year good wine
Have a taste
Mom and Dad
You asked Cynthia
and me to come
What is it about
Lewes
Selling frogs this time
Made quite a bit
Here it comes
After costs
And paying off debts
there's not much left
Still hiding it from us
Didn't make money
Yet you bought a gold bracelet
And a tri-fold phone
Lewes
We're all family
I won't beat around the bush
Daniel is short two million
for compensation
You lend the money to Daniel first
When he makes money later
He'll pay you back
Mom
Back then Daniel and Lewes
Borrowed money to start a farm
Said they'd split the profits fifty-fifty
But he kicked Lewes out
when he made money
And looked down on him constantly
How does he have the nerve now
To borrow money from Lewes
Taking an outsider's side
Ungrateful wretch
Daniel is your brother
Do you have the heart
To watch his legs get broken
for not paying
I
I don't have the money
Impossible
I saw it with my own eyes
You made over three million
After costs and what you spent
You have at least two million left
I'm keeping this money
To expand the farm
The contract is already signed
In the end
You just don't want to help
Such an important matter
Why didn't you
Discuss it with us elders
With so much money what if
You lose it all down the drain
Better lend it to Daniel
He'll pay you back when he makes it
Lending it to him is throwing it away
Who are you cursing
This time was an accident
Daniel is so outstanding
He will definitely make money later
But you
This time was just
Pure blind luck
Right brother-in-law
Starting a business is risky
How about this
You lend me the money
And keep working for me
I'll keep my word this time
Split the profits equally
No need
It's fine as it is
I won't envy you
when you make money
And if you lose money
It has nothing to do with me
You
He is your brother-in-law
How does it have nothing
to do with you
If you don't lend the money
I'll make Cynthia divorce you
I will never divorce
You
You unfilial daughter
I raised you for nothing
Cynthia
You think you're all grown up
For a man
You won't even listen to me
and your mom
If you have any conscience left
Tell Lewes to give up the money
Otherwise don't call me mom
Mom and Dad
Lewes doesn't owe our
family anything
Guess dinner is over
Let's go
Get out both of you
Lewes Cynthia
When I'm rich
Don't expect to borrow a dime